// -------------------------------------------------
// Lineage II Script Tool
// Make by HellFire, Russia, Ekaterinburg, 2005-2008
// project start at May 2005
// -------------------------------------------------

The utility is intended for work with scripts of server LineageII. It is devoted to loss of time
during manual work.

NET Framework 2.0 required.
http://download.microsoft.com/download/5/6/7/567758a3-759e-473e-bf8f-52154438565a/dotnetfx.exe

The list of features.

		* NPC Modules *
- NpcPos Maker. 
Creation of territories with npc. It is made of one coordinate and a name npc.
Support of creation of Multi zones for many npc and One zone for many npc. Support of creation Privates.
Generation of positions with spawn chance.
- NpcPch Maker:
Creation of Pch/Pch2 files necessary for work.
Creation of cache files necessary for work CacheD
- Npc Injector:
Split file to many files (one file - one npc)
Merge all files (split metod) to one npcdata.txt.
Inject one npc to npcdata.txt
- NpcPos Shifter:
You can do shift coordinates in npcpos to needed value for any direct (x, y, z).
- NpcData skill_list checker:
get skill_list from npcgrp.txt and fix npcdata.
- NpcdataRateChanger. Support: 
change rate on spoil, drop, exp, sp;
change item amount drop rate on adena, sealstones, spoil, drop
change item amount drop rate on spoil, drop to max value only or for both (min, max)
change item amount drop rate on spoil, drop only for specific items from custom list
5 mode on rate builder. 4 on drop and spoil, 1 for spoil only. "Choose what you like better!"
change rates and amount only for specific Npc type list.
- NpcPos Checker. Support: 
1) searching bad privates. Logged only.
2) searching bad privates. Logged only.
3) searching invalid makers. Logged only.
4) searching invalid dbname param. Logged only.
5) searching outsider problem.
- Npcdata Aggro Patch generator. Made npcname-e.txt with info about mob level and aggro status. Affect only for 'warrior' type.
- Npcdata Drop Checker Tool: check summary of chances of items in one group in mob drop (additional_make_multi_list={})
- Npcpos Checker: Quot Fixer. Scanning server log and fix error "failed to increase total npc because of npc quota".
- Npcpos Manor zones Generator: Generate manor zones for npcpos for all locations.
- NpcData Collision Fixer: generate file with collision_radius, collision_height params and do import this params to current npcdata.
- NpcData Analyser: analysing npcdata.txt for common params.
- [New]NpcData Passive Skill fixer: critical engine fix and enhanced module with new features.
- [New]Npcpos Viewer/Simple Editor. [Module developed by E.Koksharov, Russia, Ekaterinburg]
- [New]NpcData Herb Mob Generator. Finding mobs what must drop herbs.

		* Skill Modules *
- SkillPch Maker:
Creation of Pch/Pch2 files necessary for work.
Creation of cache files necessary for work CacheD
- Skill Injector:
Split file to many files (one file - one skill). Better metod for work with skills.
Merge all files (split metod) to one skilldata.txt.
- Skill Editor:
Simple editor for one skill. Support import skill for edit. Include all features for skill
 (ave, attr and etc).
- SkillAquire Editor: Creation new skillaquire.txt or edit exist file.
Support add/delete skills in list, commentaries and etc.
- Skilldata Effect Researcher: parsing for effect for generating file with all skilldata effects with examples.
- Skilldata Creator/SkillEnchantData Generator: generate clean skilldata.txt and SkillEnchantData.txt from client files (skilldata-e.txt and skillgrp.txt).

		* Item Modules *
- ItemPch Maker:
Creation of Pch/Pch2 files necessary for work.
Creation of cache files necessary for work CacheD
- Item Injector:
Split file to many files (one file - one item). Better metod for work with skills.
Merge all files (split metod) to one itemdata.txt.
Inject one npc to itemdata.txt.
- Default_price finder:
You can calculate default_price for item from screen (you must know town rate, castle rate and buy price
for this item)
- ItemData Fixer: now have 4 metod's:
	- check duplicate names and automaticaly renamed to [itemname_itemid]
	- check item_type. If item_type different with header type, then header type automaticaly renamed to item_type type
	Questitems checking:
	- check itemtype=questitem. If item is questitem but name not start with "[q_" then name will be renamed to [q_itemname]
	- check all itemtypes. If item is not questitem but name start with "[q_itemname]" then name will be renamed to [itemname]
	Note: Much nonquest items have q_. Example Coins [q_gold_wyrm] and etc normal quest items.
- ItemData Generator from client .Dat file. Generate a lot params with use dependence from other param.

		* AI Modules *
- AI Injector:
Split file to many files (one file - one ai). Better metod for work with ai.
Merge all files (split metod) to one ai.obj. (NO WORK correctly for full ai.obj because correct sort metod not existing).
Inject one npc class to ai.obj.  Support of recovery. Check for simple errors.
- AIMessageImporter: make export all Sxxxx. strings to file and make import all Sxxxx. to new Ai.obj from export file
- AIMessageTeleportImporter: make export (same as AIMessageImporter) all 'telposlist_...' strings to file and make importing to new Ai.obj from export file.
- AiRateChanger: change rate for getting items, sp, exp. Support log.
- container NULL pos Fixer: check AI.obj and npcdata for finding incorrect record for error "container NULL pos"
- Ai.obj Handler Line checker: Check of a file on quantity of lines in Handler.. Support log.
- Ai.obj Fixer: Check of a file on correct values in func_call, fetch_i, push_event and correction. Support log.
- Ai and NpcData Params Checker for check npcdata params (npc_ai=..) in ai.obj. Check full ai inherits tree.
- AI.obj shop list Generator for creating new shop list in Ai.obj.
- AI DeCompiler. no comments
- Raid Boss Position AI class and simple npcpos Generator.

		* Script Checker and Fixer Modules *
- Script Name Changer: allows to rename all names (skill's, npc's, item's) into names of other file. It is applied on files which send you from other developer (demand pch files for work of this method). Check all  duplicate names.
- Script Leecher: finding param in one script and write to another. Can use for exchange data from one project to another. Or import data from client files to server scripts.
- Visual Script Editor: universal editor for scripts. Support templates for edit any script types.
- .DAT Decoder/Encoder with use l2encdec and l2asm:
Full functional module for working with client .DAT files. Module use L2EncDec(r) for decrypt/encrypt and L2Asm(r) for unpack/pack data for creating (as target idea) config files with old/basis standarts/formats.
You must SELF to create definition config's for working of feature "L2Asm<->Txt". Or you can use tool as simple GUI interface for l2asm and l2encdec (encode/decode, pack/unpack).
- Script Param Value Searcher: search all definitions for param. Use for finding all existing values for param in script. Second, can use for creating L2SM Editor config file. And etc.
- L2ScriptMaker Script Generator: can generate clean server config file from .dat client file
- Recipe Generator: create new server recipe.txt script from client recipe-e.txt file
- Script ID-Name Shower: searching Name for Id, or Id for Name (support itemdata, npcdata, skilldata). Idea by Hint
- [New]Script Analyzer: Simple checking for knowns symbols what must have 'open' and 'close' symbols. Example, [ and ], { and }
- [New]HTML Checker: module for finding html dialog and checking of availability this file and server folder.

		* Other Modules *
- Doorarea Maker: Creation doordata for one door. You need have only one pos and known door parameters.
- EventData Generator for creating new event.
- Multisell Generator for creating new multisell or import and edit your exchange list.
- AreaData Generator: to generate areadata zones.
- Exec Injector: Allows to apply a patch (self simple format) to any Exec file. Support of recovery. Support
of patches with absolute addressing.
- Authentifycation Blowfish Change Key Tool: you can see and change blowfish auth key in l2auth service and in client engine.dll
- Html Button Designer: can do from simple button - button with style (size, background) in all html files in folder
- QuestComp-e generator for 'CachedScripts' folder
- QuestPch/Pch2 Builder. Required itemdata.txt, questdata-e.txt and ai.obj for creating this files.
- Superpoint.bin Builder. See superpoint.bin file in text and build new Superpoint.bin from text file.
- GeoIndex Generator: small module for fast creating geo_index.txt file into GeoData folder.
- Geodata name from Location converter: find geodata name from coordinates.
- GetTestPoint Finder and Geodata Bug file gererator: scanning server ERR logs and generating geo_bug (xx_xx_bug.txt) files
- [New]SQL Query Manager: simple query manager for remotely using sql scripts with control values
- [New]LogParser: scanning LogD logs. Support enchanced filtering, load in memory (for fast finding) or save immediately to file. Support logs explaination (name items, mobs, skills and actions)
- [New]HTML (Dialog) Designer: creating and edit npc dialog
